Humans can be poor judges of their own ability.
人类不太能正确评估自身的能力。
So, you might not be as good, or as bad, as you think you are.
所以，你可能并不像自己认为的那样优秀或糟糕。
Psychologists have found the less expertise you have in something, the more likely you are to overestimate your competence in it.
心理学家发现，你对某件事的专业知识越少，就越有可能高估自己在这方面的能力。
And in a digital era where self-assured social media influencers give you 'life hacks', and face-to-face conversation is more limited, this psychological phenomenon seems important to remember.
在一个自信的社交媒体网红向你传授"生活妙招"、面对面交流更加受限的数字时代，这种心理现象似乎很重要，值得铭记。
This concept is called the Dunning-Kruger effect, named after the psychologists David Dunning and Justin Kruger.
这个概念被称为邓宁-克鲁格效应，以心理学家戴维·邓宁和贾斯汀·克鲁格的名字命名。
Back in the 90s, they found a correlation between a person's lack of skills and ability and a lack of awareness of lack of ability.
早在90年代，他们发现一个人的技能和能力缺乏与对自身能力缺乏的认知之间存在关联。
They are ignorant to their own limitations.
他们对自己的局限性一无所知。
This plays out in various areas of life, such as in medical diagnosis.
这种情况在生活的各个领域都有体现，比如在医疗诊断中。
For example, Dunning told BBC Radio 4 that, one third of the time, doctors disagree with patients who self-diagnose using internet sources rather than seeing a medical professional.
例如，邓宁告诉BBC广播4台，医生有三分之一的情况与那些使用网络资源自我诊断而非去看医生的患者意见相左。
Whether it's judging jokes, logical reasoning, or grammar, the pattern is the same: the less skilled you are, the more over-confident you are.
无论是评判笑话、逻辑推理还是语法，情况都是一样的：你技能越差，你就越过度自信。
On the flip side is intellectual humility.
另一方面是智力谦逊。
This means having a modest or low view of your importance or abilities.
这意味着对自己的重要性或能力持谦虚或较低的看法。
Elizabeth J. Krumrei-Mancuso, Professor of Psychology at Pepperdine University, found that a higher willingness to acknowledge cognitive limitations, and the ability to embrace diverse perspectives, is connected with a more accurate perception of intelligence.
佩珀代因大学心理学教授伊丽莎白·J·克鲁姆雷-曼库索发现，更愿意承认认知局限以及接纳多元观点的能力，与对智力更准确的认知有关。
How can we use this knowledge to help us in everyday life?
我们如何在日常生活中运用这一知识呢？
Tenelle Porter, a psychologist at Rowan University, told the BBC that knowing this "opens us up to being intellectually humble, to admitting everything that we don't yet know".
罗文大学心理学家特内尔·波特告诉BBC，了解这一点"让我们能够保持智力上的谦逊，承认所有我们尚不知道的事情"。
And current studies suggest that those with higher intellectual humility are more open to negotiating, compromising and exploring information.
目前的研究表明，智力谦逊程度较高的人更愿意协商、妥协和探索信息。
So, embrace the unknown and remember, there's always more to learn.
所以，拥抱未知，记住，总有更多东西值得学习。